Alejandra Schibli /

Partner

Practice Area: Insurance Law

alejandra.schibli@ocl.cl

Alejandra is a founding partner leading the firm's Insurance Law area. She has sound experience in legal risk audits and insurance programs for local and regional insurance tenders and renewals. She has also been counsel in adjustments and subsequent indemnity negotiations. She was named Star Lawyer in 2017-2018 by Acritas, Independently Rated Lawyers.

WORK HISTORY

2017 - present / Ovalle Consejeros Legales

2014 - 2017 / Ovalle y Compañía Limitada - Director, Insurance area

2010 - 2014 / Ovalle y Compañía Limitada

2003 - 2010 / Estudio Carvallo

EXPERIENCE

- Handled large losses for the insured from the February 27, 2010 earthquake.
- Design and management of more than 50 policy tenders of all types, such as All Risk of Physical Loss, Interruption Damages, Freight (traditional model, stock throughput and fresh fruit exports), General Civil Liability, Director and Officer Insurance, Credit Insurance and Group Life and Health Insurance.
- Design and management of regional insurance program tenders of companies in Chile, Argentina, Bolivia, Peru and Colombia.

EDUCATION

B.A. in Legal and Social Sciences, graduating summa cum laude, Diego Portales University. Admissions: 2003.

MEMBERSHIPS

- Chilean Chapter of the International Association of Insurance Law (AIDA).
- Chilean Bar Association.

LANGUAGES

Spanish and English

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alejandra-schibli-26035241/